as the tech revolution continues to
destroy old media the Internet is
fueling a new intellectual awakening
television made people look stupider
than they were it turns out that people
are smarter with longer attention spans
then we thought I'm a journalist and
filmmaker for many years I made
documentaries for the likes of the BBC
and channel 4 but I don't think the
mainstream media can provide the level
of analysis and insight we need for the
extraordinary times we're going through
where the old structures that made sense
of the world break down it's like we're
entering just entering into the
underworld and it's a descent we're
feeling everything starting to shake and
the center cannot hold
and when our ways of thinking break down
it's the rebels and the Renegades who
dare to think differently who are needed
to reboot the system and so what's
happening is that people are perceiving
because it's becoming increasingly
obvious that all of these artifacts of
the way that we've gone about doing
civilization are breaking down and
failing in a way that is no longer easy
to pretend isn't happening and so as a
consequence this triggers a deep
visceral sense and that's a good thing
right because that deep visceral sense
is the return to the aluminum the return
to the mystery the shift that we are on
the precipice of is not like the shift
from the Dark Ages to the Enlightenment
it's like more like a shift from single
cell to multicellular life these are the
people and ideas rebel wisdom is
searching out to try to make sense of
the growing chaos the evolution screwed
up it handed us the tools to recognize
that we don't have to value the game
that it is playing and that we can now
repurpose the hardware to something
that's actually worthwhile that's what I
actually had hope in is that if enough
people can come to that realization then
then we wake up and not in some
evangelical megachurch kind of way of
being born again but in in a truly
initiatory way being born again of like
I know my purpose I know my part
and I'm willing to practice resurrection
I'm willing to offer my life fully and
freely in love in every moment and then
we're invincible like then we can turn
things on a dime it's also about trying
to create a new form of conversation one
based on genuine dialogue letting go of
ideology and fix ideas so we want to be
a place that hosts this new form of
conversation both online and at our
events check out our films join the
conversation and to get early access to
some great films and exclusive content
please consider supporting us on patreon
[Music]